Eddy Uwambaje

Full stack web developer

Rwanda, Rubavu

Education

Software development

Jun 2018 - Sep 2021

Lycee de Kicukiro Apade

- Responsive web design
- Data structures and algorithms

Employment

Engineering Apprentice

Feb 2022 - Present

Andela, Kigali, Rwanda

- Worked on my personal web portfolio with the help of Andela managers and team leads.
- Worked within a team using Reactjs on Travel agency
- - Assigned to be a team lead for several sprints within a team of four developers.
- Gained experience working with distributed teams on real-world products and active users

Software Developer

Oct 2021 - Jan 2022

Filmnet Rwanda, Kigali, Rwanda

- Installation and deployment of a developed management software and the website
- - Designing of the website's frontend alongside with bug and fixing software support.
- - Integrate continuous feedback together with the customer
- - Analyzation of code quality and continuous code reviews

Frontend developer

Sep 2021 - Feb 2022

Sillion africa, Kigali,Rwanda

- Write modern, performant, maintainable code for a diverse array of client and internal projects
- · Work with a variety of different languages, frameworks, platforms, and content management systems such as JavaScript, React, PHP
- Communicate with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, designers, producers, and clients on a daily basis

Career summary

A passionate full stack web developer and a freelance software engineer from Rwanda with 3+ years of experience. my passion for software lies with dreaming up ideas and making them come true with elegant interfaces. I take great care in the experience, architecture, and code quality of the things I build.

Details

Website

uwambajeeddy.herokuapp.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/eddy-uwambaje -920a27228/

Github

github.com/uwambajeddy

Skills

React.js

Node.Js

Material UI

Docker

Sass

Bootstrap

Figma

Unit testing

Git

Github

Sequelize - Postgres

MongoDB

Languages

Javascript